走吧 卡梅隆
Come on, Cameron.
- 是爸吗？    - 不是
- Is it Dad?    - No.
来 我们做饭
Come on. Let's cook.
我们吃什么？
What are we eating?
义大利面？
Spaghetti?
或是...
Or...
...义大利面？
..spaghetti?
来  帮忙我做酱料
Come on. Help me make the sauce.
琳赛 你搞什么？
Lindsey, what are you doing?
接电话
Answer the phone.
你不可以不理我 好吗？ 他也是我儿子  我...
You can't ignore me, alright? He's my kid too. I have...
好 我很抱歉 行吗？
Alright, look. I'm sorry, OK?
就...就让他跟我说话
Just... just let me talk to him.
我不是故意打他的 好吗？
I didn't mean to hit him, OK?
那是个意外 好吗？
It was an accident, alright?
我绝对不会故意伤害他的
I would never intentionally hurt him like that.
这你也知道 是吗？我也道歉了
You know that. OK? And I've apologised.
你到底想让我怎么样？
What the hell do you want from me?
宝贝？
Honey?
- 你没事吧？    - 马上好 妈
- Everything OK in there? - One second, Mom.
你没事吧？
You OK?
妈？
Mom?
妈！
Mom!
怎么了？怎么了？
What? What?
不！
No!
卡梅隆Cameron?
# Sail! #
喔  可能很重要呢
Oh. Could be important.
- 会比现在更重要吗？    - 不会
- More important than right now? - No.
- 有事吗？    - 对
- Can I help you? - Yeah.
你应该接他妈的电话
You could have answered your damn phone.
该走了 亨利
It's time to go, Henry.
- 你怎么知道我的名字？    - 你要我叫警卫来吗？
- How do you know my name? - You want me to call security?
不 等等 等等 等等 等等
No. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
你是谁？这是怎么回事？
Who are you? What's this about?
看看你的表  什么时间了？
Look at your watch. What's it say?
1:46.
你来这里后就一直是1:46分
It's been 1:46 since you came in here.
我的表停了  那又怎样？
My watch froze. So what?
我向你保证 这里的每块表和钟
I guarantee you every watch and clock
都停在相同的这个时间
in this place says the exact same thing.
行了 你这疯子
Alright, crazy guy.
警卫！你该走了
Security! Time for you to go.
你知道这是什么吗？
You know what this is?
这是对你很重要的东西
It's something important to you.
它可以帮你想起你的真实身份
It's to help you remember who you really are.
当我升格成为合伙人的时候 我哥哥送我的
My brother gave me this when I became partner.
没错  你是个律师 你工作得很勤劳
That's right. You're a lawyer, Henry. You work all the time.
你没有社交生活  你不外出
You have no social life. You don't go out.
而且痛苦的事实是
And to be painfully honest,
女人从来不会正眼看你一下
women don't even look in your general direction.
我们不在夜店里
We're not in a nightclub.
你也没有被美女围着
You're not surrounded by beautiful women.
醒醒 伙计
Wake up, buddy.
我们在你的意识里
We're in your head.
是时候你该离开了
It's time for you to go.
这太粗鲁了
That's rude.
Whoa!
他们的力量是你给的 亨利 你可以收回去
You gave them the power, Henry. You can take it back.
他在骗你 宝贝
He's just messing with you, babe.
Ooh!
你只有这两下子吗？
That all you got?
- 在找 玛姬吗？    - 她在哪里？
- Looking for Maggie? - Where is she?
她说 她对于你儿子的事很遗憾
She says she's so very sorry about your little boy.
- 操你妈！    - 把他带走
- Fuck you! - Get him out of here.
- 希望下次好运些      - 看看窗外 亨利
- Better luck next time. - Look out the window, Henry.
有什么不对劲吗？亨利？
Something wrong, Henry?
快走
- Come on. - Oh...
别看他们 继续走
Don't look at them. Keep moving.
我快疯了 快疯了
I'm losing my mind. Losing my mind.
- 狗屎  - 什么？什么？
- Shit. - What? What?
你真以为我会让你那么轻易得手吗？
Did you really think I was gonna make it that easy for you?
- 你最喜欢的颜色是什么？    - 没有
- What's your favourite colour? - I don't have a favourite.
你车子的颜色是什么？你最好的西装呢？
What colour's your car? Your best suit?
- 最爱的毛衣？拜托！    - 什么？
- Favourite sweater? Come on! - What?
我需要真实的东西 来制造出一个逃生的路
I need to make an escape route, something true.
- 回答问题      - 绿色
- Answer the question. - Green.
那是他妈的从哪里冒出来的？
Where the fuck did that come from?
快走！
Come on!
这是他妈的怎么一回事？
What the hell is this?
这是我们击溃幻觉的地方
This is where we break down the illusion.
如果你想醒过来 就跳下去
If you want to wake up from this, jump.
- 亨利 把门打开      - 去他妈的
- Henry, open the door! - Fuck that.
把门打开！
Open the door!
- 亨利 让我进去      - 可是 宝贝...
- Henry, let me in! - But, baby...
可是你的眼睛是黑的
But your eyes are black.
宝贝 他在你饮料里下药了
Baby, he slipped something into your drink.
亨利！马上跳  你不会有第二次机会了
Henry! Jump, now. You won't get another chance.
- 你不能强迫我这样做      - 我不能强迫你做任何事
- You can't make me do this. - I can't make you do anything.
你必须相信这会有用
You have to believe it will work.
开门！让我进去！
Open the door! Let me in!
拜托  开门！让我进去！
Come on. Open the door! Let me in!
- 你先跳      - 如果有用的话 我会跳
- You go first. - If that would help, I would.
但你必须做这个抉择
But you have to make the choice.
跟我走 亨利
Come with me, Henry.
不！
No!
不！不！
No! No!
好了  重见光明 老大
Alright. Rise and shine, boss.
你成功了  又一个吃土去了 嗯？
You did it. Another one bites the dust, huh?
欢迎回到现实
Welcome back to reality.
我竖了几只指头？
How many fingers am I holding up?
奥利弗 把你那混蛋拇指从我脸前拿开
Oliver, get your damn thumb out of my face.
好了  你没事了
Alright. You'll live.
玛姬 不在那里
Maggie wasn't there.
经过15次潜入(指进入他人意识)后 我们失去她的踪迹了
After 15 dives, we've lost her.
我知道
I know.
可是我们会找到她的 她不可能永远藏起来
But we'll get her. She can't hide forever.
她在戏弄我 奥利弗
She's taunting me, Oliver.
对她来说这是个游戏
It's a game to her.
你
You.
是你在我梦里
You were in my dream.
那不是个狗日的梦
Wasn't a fucking dream.
Arggh!
你可能会死在那里 你知道的 是吗？
This is gonna be the end of you. You know that, right?
下次我们要减少药量
We'll lower the dosage next time.
不能减少药量
Can't lower the dosage.
问题在于你 老大
The problem is you, boss.
拜托  看看那警卫把你的手腕弄的
Come on. Look what the bouncer did to your wrist.
看 你在逐渐陷溺 那太真实了
Look, you're adapting. It's becoming too real.
我跟你说 如果你不更加小心
I'm telling you, if you don't watch it,
你会陷在里面回不来
you're gonna get stuck in there.
你不是叫我示弱吧？是吗 奥利弗？
You're not going soft on me, are you, Oliver?
我只是说说罢了...我不知道
I'm just saying... I don't know.
休息一、两个月 让你的身体复原 知道吧？
Take a month or two off. Let your body recover, you know?
玛姬 不在那里
Maggie wasn't there.
她为什么不在那里？
Why wasn't she there?
对撞车祸导致母子死亡 父亲命危
嘿 我挖了这家伙被附身前去过的每个地方
Hey - I dug up all the places
our guy visited before the possession.
除了他的办公室
Aside from his office,
他都耗在星巴克 和低档的脱衣舞吧
he hung out at Starbucks and low-rent strip clubs.
OK 我们去查查
OK. Let's check it out.
我要 亨利 去的每个晚上的监视录像
I'm gonna need surveillance tape on the nights Henry visited.
我要知道他在脱衣舞吧是跟谁鬼混
I want to see who he's hanging out with at those strip clubs.
我想我刚听到 奥利弗 自愿要去
I think I just heard Oliver volunteer.
喔！这件事你可付不起我的工资  不干
Oh! You cannot pay me enough money. No.
而且 我今晚有个现实的约会
Besides, I have a date with reality tonight.
哦 听起来很有趣喔
Well, that sounds intriguing.
她的名字叫什么？
What's her name?
- 萨拉      - 等一下
- Sara. - Wait a minute.
- 那 Jenny 怎么了？    - Jenny？
- What happened to Jenny? - Jenny?
- 那 詹妮 怎么了？    - 詹妮？
你跟她分手 就因为她要去跳伞？
You broke up with her because she wanted to go skydiving?
是啊 你知道我恐高的
Yeah. You know how I feel about high places.
Hm.
奥利弗 我没教过你吗？
Oliver, have I taught you nothing?
天呐 我几乎忘了
Oh, my God. I almost forgot.
有个叫 卡米拉 等着要见你
There's someone named Camilla that's here to see you.
她说她来自 安德雷德大主教辖区
She said she's from the Andrade Archdiocese.
那是...梵谛冈？
The... the Vatican?
- 哇 她好辣      - 呕！
- Whoa. She's hot.    - Ugh!
那么 要我赶她走吗？
So should I tell her to go away?
告诉她 她有五分钟
Tell her she's got five minutes.
我盯着你的工作有一段时间了
I've been following your work for quite some time.
我知道你在六个月内 完成了三次驱魔
I understand you've done three exorcisms
in the last six months.
我比较喜欢用“驱逐”来形容  没错
I prefer to call them evictions. Yes.
你为什么来这儿？
Why are you here?
我的上司们需要个替身帮忙
My superiors need an incarnate.
那 费利克斯·纳兹 怎么了？
What happened to Felix Nazra?
他们认为学生可能更胜过老师
They thought perhaps the student has surpassed the teacher.
或者他们受不了你们导致的死亡人数
Or they just got sick of the body counts you leave behind.
这情况需要的是手术刀 不是铁鎚
This situation needs a scalpel, not a hammer.
请便
Please.
(几十万美金！)
卡米拉 对吗？
Camilla, right?
你在浪费你的时间 我不会干的
You're wasting your time. It's not gonna happen.
我不替梵谛冈做事
I don't clock in for the Vatican.
你和教会之间有什么冲突？
What do you have against the Church?
你有多少时间听？
How much time you got?
听着 我不认为我的所为属于任何宗教
Look, I just don't believe what I do
belongs to any one religion.
- 驱逐恶魔？    - 不 对你来说 那是恶魔
- Exorcising demons? - No, to you, it's a demon.
对别人 那是个不洁的灵魂 那是 Jinn或是 Orisha
To others, it's an unclean spirit, it's Jinn, it's Orisha.
Jinn 上帝创造天使和人类之外的第三个物种;
Orisha 非洲约鲁巴(Yoruba)宗教传说中 大神显灵时反射出的另一个灵体
那是...随便你挑吧 OK？
It's... Take your pick, OK?
真的 那只是个寄生虫灵体
Really, it's just a parasitic entity
无形体的转移
in a non-corporeal transference.
如果我告诉你
What if I told you
一个寄生虫灵体附在了一个小男孩身上？
a parasitic entity just took a little boy?
我会说 那不是我的问题
I would say it ain't my problem.
那如果我告诉你 那是 玛姬 呢？
What if I told you it was Maggie?
我想这能引起你的注意
I thought that would get your attention.
Hmm...
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
她躲在妓院里的一具半死不活的身体里
She's holed up in a half-dead body
等着被消灭
in a whorehouse,just ready to be taken down.
你需要一个真人替身帮忙 因为圣 Vicinius 之环
You need an incarnate because the ring of St Vicinius
和一片耶苏的裹尸布 这次都没效了
and a piece of holy cloth just won't cut it this time.
抱歉 我不知道你在说什么？(译者也不知道 哈)
I'm sorry. I don't know what you're talking about.
那我就挑明了说
Then let me make it crystal-clear.
你上司上次派来的辣妹
The last beautiful woman your superiors sent here
拎着同样的胡萝卜 说“我们确定那是 玛姬  ”
dangled the same carrot - "We're sure it's Maggie."
结果 意外呀 那不是
Well, surprise, it wasn't,
只是个小妖怪... 附身在一个乡下家庭主妇
just some lesser succubus who... turned a suburban housewife
把她转变成一个毒虫割喉凶人
into a heroin-addicted throat-cutter
差点把我和我的助手们都杀了
who nearly killed me and my assistants.
听着 我对他们上次派来的女人毫无所知
Look, I have no idea about the last woman they sent.
我只知道有个高等恶魔
What I do know is that I have an archdemon
附身在一个无辜的11岁男孩身上
possessing the body of an innocent 11-year-old boy.
我们相信那恶魔就是你称为 玛姬 的灵体
We believe that arch is that entity you call Maggie.
所以你和你的助手们真想抓她的话
So if you and your assistants really want to take her out,
打个电话给我
give me a call.
可别等太久
Just don't wait too long.
那男孩活不过三天了
The boy won't survive more than three days.
恩伯Ember.
是她吗？
Is it her?
进来再说
Why don't you come inside?
这些都是梵谛冈的钱买的？
So this is what Vatican money buys?
我可以给你喝些什么？
Can I offer you anything?
我只是要知道 费利克斯  那是不是 玛姬？
I just need to know, Felix. Is it Maggie?
不确定
Uncertain.
这次教会不准我参与
The Church has excluded me from this one.
为什么？因为他们无法容忍被害死的是小孩子？
Why? Because they can't stomach the murder of a child?
或者 因为他们担心这次会掩盖不住？
Or because they're afraid they can't cover it up this time?
恩伯 别忘了你在哪里？
Ember, remember where you are.
在哪里？
And where's that?
和一个朋友在一起
With a friend.
还记得我教你关于如何潜入
Remember the first thing I taught you
一个人意识中的第一件事吗？
about entering other people's minds?
人类很容易被他们的需求和欲望所蒙蔽
Humans are easily blinded by their needs and desires.
记住这点会对你很有帮助
It would serve you well to remember that.
我们都有各自的方法和动机
We each have our methods. We each have our motives.
如果你不知道那是她
This conversation wouldn't have lasted this long
这段谈话就不会延续这么长
if you didn't know it was her.
你知道是她 是吗？
You know it's her, don't you?
是
Yes.
可是如果你还没跟教会谈过...
But if you haven't spoken to the Church...
...你是怎么知道的？
..how do you know?
我要给你看些东西
I want to show you something.
那门是10公分厚的玻璃
The door's glass is four inches thick.
即使是犀牛都撞不破
A rhino couldn't crack it.
里外总共有12个录像头 24小时监控
There are 12 cameras inside and out, monitored 24 hours a day.
了不起  那是什么？
Fantastic. What is it?
我发现光亮会激怒它
I've found the light agitates it.
那是个人？把个人他妈的关在那里？
Is that a person? Got somebody fucking locked up in there?
记得去年失踪的那个驱魔人吗？
Remember the incarnate who disappeared last year?
鲁卡·雷奇Luka Rejick.
操！
Shit!
他已经不是 鲁卡·雷奇 很长时间了
This hasn't been Luka Rejick in a long time, I'm afraid.
你在对他做什么？
What are you doing with him?
它们知道我们很多事
They know a lot about us.
不是该轮到我们从它们那里学到更多事吗？
Isn't it time we learned more about them?
老天！
Jesus!
你知道它们试图渗透人类 已经很多年了吗？
Did you know they've tried to infiltrate our ranks for years?
它也告诉了我关于那男孩 以及 玛姬
He told me. He also told me about the boy, about Maggie.
- 这就是我知道的原因      - 那我还等什么？
- That's how I know. - What am I waiting for?
你想知道如何打败她吗？
Don't you want to know how to beat her?
知道吗？恩伯 有时候...
You know, Ember, sometimes...
...为了避免进入比死亡更糟的境地
..in order to avoid a fate worse than death,
你必须选择死亡
you must choose death instead.
这要感谢鲁卡我才能制造出这个
And thanks to Luka here, I was able to develop this.
- 那是啥？    - C-79
- What is it? - C-79.
这试管里装的是片刻的清醒
In this vial is a moment of clarity.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
这是从我们这位朋友的血液中的部分成份 制成的血清
It's a serum made in part from the blood of our friend here.
如果 玛姬 占了上风 我希望她不会
Should Maggie get the upper hand, and I hope she doesn't,
这可以给你十秒钟的清醒时间
this will give you approximately 10 seconds of lucidity
去做必须做的事
in order to do what needs to be done.
一但注射了这个 你会醒来一段足够的时间
Inject this and you'll wake up with just enough time
在她把你永恒困住之前 结束自己的生命
to end your life before she traps you forever.
你真认为我会用这个？
You seriously think I'm gonna use this?
费利克斯
Felix... Look, Felix...
我非常感激你教我的一切
I appreciate everything you taught me.
可是你的毒药你自己留着吧
But keep your poison.
我还没打算死
I'm not planning on dying.
Hello?
有个叫 卡米拉 等着要见你
There's someone named Camilla that's here to see you.
我们谈谈
Let's talk.
那男孩名字叫 卡梅隆·斯帕罗
The boy's name is Cameron Sparrow.
他父母最近刚离婚
His parents just recently divorced.
母亲是荷兰裔
The mother is originally from Holland.
她有对那位父亲的法院限制令
She has a restraining order against the father,
一个酒鬼 - 他弄断了那男孩的手臂
an alcoholic - he broke the boy's arm.
那男孩有精神分裂、幻觉的病史吗？
Does Cameron have any history of schizophrenia, delusion?
- 任何我应该知道的病史？    - 没有  这份资料里没有
- Any meds I should know about? - No. Nothing in his records.
母亲听到他在厨房里尖叫
The mother heard him scream in the kitchen.
她到厨房后 发现了这个
When she arrived... she found this.
那男孩扭断了她的颈子
The boy broke her neck.
当然 我们派出了最好的驱魔师
Of course, we sent in the best exorcists
去处理这个情况 可是...
to handle the situation, but...
他们都失败了
..they failed.
- 它是如何转换驱体的？    - 身体接触
- How does it transfer? - Physical contact.
经由它的受害者判断
Judging from its trail of victims,
它只能附身弱者 - 小孩、老人、病人
it can only possess the weak - kids, the elderly, sick people.
我没有告诉那位母亲 关于你和 玛姬 间的关系
I haven't told the mother about your connection with Maggie.
那男孩被隔离了吗？
Is the boy quarantined?
已经一个星期 没有任何人碰触过 卡梅隆
No-one has touched Cameron in a week.
- 那母亲的意志如何？    - 她很疲累了
- How's the mother's will? - She's tired.
她已经受了太多  我们不让她接近那孩子
She's been through a lot. We're keeping her away from the boy.
我已经回答这问题几百遍了
I've already answered these questions a thousand times.
- 你是谁？    - 斯帕罗太太...
- Who are you? - Mrs Sparrow...
叫 琳赛 就好 别太太了
Just Lindsey, no Mrs.
琳赛 我们请 恩伯 博士来帮你
Lindsey, we brought Dr Ember to help you.
另一个教士 太好了
Another priest. Great.
不 他不是教士
No, he's not a priest.
他就像个治疗师
He's like a therapist.
我来这里不是要治疗你儿子的精神疾病
I'm not here to treat your son for mental illness.
- 那你来做什么？    - 我是来评估...
- Then why are you here? - To evaluate whether or not...
恩伯 博士有最先进的方法
Dr Ember has employed a cutting-edge method
去帮助他的病人
for helping his patients.
他能进入我们去不了的地方
He can go places we can't,
拿到我们无法获得的资料
get information that'd otherwise be unavailable to us.
你是来进行驱魔的 对吗？
You're here to perform an exorcism, right?
让我们直话直说 我不搞驱魔那套
Let's get this straight off the bat. I don't do exorcisms.
我不使用教会那些方法
I don't use religious methods to treat the symptoms.
我潜入受害者的意识里
I go inside the victim's mind
去治疗疾病
to treat the disease.
我不从外界驱赶那些灵体
I don't compel these entities from the outside.
我从内部驱逐它们
I evict them...
..from the inside.
你驱逐它们？
You evict them?
附在你儿子身上的灵体 没有真正的力量
The entity that is holding your son has no real power.
它只是个寄生虫
It's a parasite.
它吸食你儿子的能量
It feeds off your son's energy.
要做这件事 它必须把他困在梦境里
But in order to do that, it has to hold him in a dream state.
即使他的眼睛是睁开的 而且会说话
Even if his eyes are open and he's speaking,
你儿子还是在睡眠状态 - 那个灵体控制着他
your son is asleep - the entity is controlling him.
要维持住控制
In order to keep that control,
它必须使他相信梦是真的
it has to convince him his dream is real.
它是让 卡梅隆 相信是身处在另一个现实中 来控制他？
It's holding Cameron by...
..convincing him he's in another reality?
对
Yes.
经由使用暗示法
Through suggestion.
它搜索他的意识
It rifles through his mind
然后把他最想要的给他 可是那都是假的
and shows him what he wants most, but it's all a lie.
我戳穿谎言 撕破骗局
I tear down the lies.
只要 卡梅隆 认知了事实 那灵体就失去了控制力
Once Cameron sees the truth, the entity loses its power.
那灵体会发生什么事？
What happens to the entity?
它会试图进入离它最近的活人
It'll try to jump into the nearest living host.
如果它没法找到另一个宿主 它就会死
If it can't find a host, it dies.
你以前做过同样的事？
And you've done this before?
喔 天呐
Oh, God.
OK.
哈罗 神父
Hello, Father.
那男孩几天没吃东西了
The boy hasn't eaten in days.
你何不去休息一下？
Why don't you take a break?
你看起来需要休息
You look like you need some rest.
他行的
He's OK.
你最好在客厅里等
It might be best if you waited in the living room.
- 可我想看看他      - 我知道  我知道  可是...
- But I want to see him. - I know. I know. But...
你必须信任我们  他会没事的 事情会解决的
You have to trust us. He'll be fine. It's gonna be OK.
这只是在评估
This is just an evaluation.
如果我无法确认那是 玛姬 我就走人
If I can't confirm this is Maggie, I'm outta here.
哈罗 恩伯 博士
Hello, Dr Ember.
你知道我是谁？
You know who I am?
感觉如何？
How does it feel?
感觉什么？
How does what feel?
失去你所爱的人
To lose the one you love.
OK.
我们已经证实了你知道我是谁
We've established that you know who I am.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我曾经被称为 Ash
I've been known as Ash.
其他人叫我瘟疫
Others have called me Plague.
大洪水(圣经中的)之后 (这魔已存在几千年了)
After the Great Deluge,
当天使们夺走了我最渴望的人类女子
when the angels took the mortal woman, I was Desire.
你觉得这很好玩？
Is this fun for you?
圣水、十字架、无所事事 变得如此...
Holy water, crucifixes and idle threats get so...
...枯燥无味
..dull.
你到底要什么？
What do you want?
你必须比这再加把劲
You're gonna have to try harder than that.
不  我没空跟你玩这个
No. I don't have time for this.
很好！
Good!
我会折磨所有你爱的人
Ah.
所以你是记得的
So you do remember.
Hey. Hey, hey.
嘿 你要去哪？那男孩怎样了？
Hey, where are you going? What about the boy?
不 不 不.......
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
等等
Wait.
是她吗？
Is it her?
我知道你家人发生的事
I know what happened to your family.
别再提我的家人
Don't you ever mention my family.
可是如果这是个高等恶魔
But if this is an archdemon,
必须要通知教会
the Church needs to know.
大量的人命可能会有危险
A lot of lives could be in jeopardy.
那就别挡着我的路 让我带我的团队来
Then move out of my way so I can get my team in here.
我是你的话 我会锁紧那道门
Then I'd lock that door, if I were you.
我要来找你了
I'm coming for you.
教会很高兴你来帮忙
The Church is pleased that you have come to help.
帮忙？我是在猎杀
Helping? I'm hunting.
不好意思 这有必要吗？
Excuse me, but is this necessary?
为什么我不能和我儿子呆在同一个房间里？
Why can I not be in the same room as my son?
当屎撞上了电扇 (意思有大事发生了)
When the shit hits the fan,
我要每个人都在这里 别妨碍到我
I'm gonna need everybody in here out of my hair.
这样比较安全 相信我
It's safer that way, believe me.
你们可以看到影像了
You should see an image.
喔 卡梅隆
Oh, Cameron.
这都是些什么？
What is all this stuff?
嗯...这是我们用来监视 恩伯 博士潜入时的状况
Um... this is what we use to monitor Dr Ember during dives.
看到吗？我们每个人都像个 Wi-Fi 的热点
See, each of us is like a wi-fi hot spot,
我们的脑部发出看不见的能量场
and our brains give off an invisible field of energy.
你看到这里的这团云吗？
You see this cloud right here?
有些人称这叫“电辉”或“灵魂”
Some people call this an aura or a soul,
其实这只是一团独特的电离子
but really what it is is just a cluster of unique ions,
而我们每个人都有自己独自的频率
and each of us has our own frequency.
这是 恩伯 博士的 这是 卡梅隆 的
So this is Dr Ember's and this is Cameron's.
你看到 卡梅隆 里的黑斑吗？那就是那个寄生虫
You see the black streaks in Cameron's? That's the parasite.
如果受害者很虚弱 它就可以和他们的频率挂上勾
If a victim is weak, it can hook right into their frequency.
喔 天呐
Oh, God.
我们就是用这监视它 直到我们能够驱逐它
We just use this to monitor it until we can evict it.
那些是做什么的？
What's all that for?
这是用来降低他的心跳和脑电波
Uh, this is gonna lower his heart rate and EEG
进入迟缓状态 让脑部尽可能接近死亡状态
to a stasis state, leaving the brain
as close to death as physically possible.
当我按下 REM(快速动眼睡眠阶段) 我就能马上进入 卡梅隆 的潜意识
When I hit REM, I'll ride into Cameron's subconscious,
开始拆穿幻象
begin dismantling the illusion.
问题是 在我的心跳停止前
The trick is I only have eight minutes
我只有八分钟的时间 那可算不上是个长时间啊
before my heart gives out, which isn't a lot of time.
有的时候 我们很走运 那容易得就像修个小故障
Sometimes we get lucky. It's as easy as the glitch.
- 小故障？    - 时间的小故障
- The glitch? - The time glitch.
我们发现 时间在潜意识中是没有意义的
We've discovered that time is meaningless in the subconscious,
所以 手表、时钟、任何显示时间的装置
so watches, clocks, anything that tells time,
都冻结在受害者被附身的那一刻
freezes at the time of the victim's possession.
我会没事的
It'll be OK.
我会救出你的儿子
I'm gonna help your son.
好了 老大  你可以进去了
OK, boss. You're good to go.
把这区净空 以防它想转换
Keep this area clear in case he tries to jump.
你知道该怎么做的
You know the drill.
别让那男孩碰触你或任何人
Don't let the boy touch you or anyone else.
也别让我碰触你或任何人
Don't let me touch you or anyone else.
奥利弗 我一但接近心跳停止
Oliver, I get anywhere near flatlining,
你就用纳洛酮 (一种药物) 把我拉出来
you yank my ass out with the Narcan.
是 逃脱法宝就在这儿 老大
Yeah. I've got the escape hatch right here, boss.
只用在绝对必要的情况下
Only if you absolutely have to.
恩伯 博士
Dr Ember.
祝你好运
Good luck in there.
谢谢
Thank you.
恩伯 博士 有你加入真是太好了
Dr Ember.So nice of you to join us.
开始计时了 老大
Starting the clock, boss.
准备好了吗？恩伯 博士
Are you ready, Dr Ember?
那就开始游戏吧
Then let the games begin.
很好 卡梅隆 保持这样 下一个扔快速球 伙计
Nice, Cameron. Keep it going. Fastball next, buddy.
正中本垒板 好极了！
Over the plate. Nice!
接得好
Nice catch.
漂亮
Beautiful.
他怎样？
How is he?
还有七分钟
Seven minutes to go.
目前为止 很好
So far, so good.
卡梅隆Cameron.
卡梅隆 听着 我知道你不认识我
Cameron. Listen, I know you don't know me.
但我是来帮你的
But I'm here to help you.
我只是想谈谈
I just want to talk.
有什么不对劲吗？
What's wrong?
你在...
You're...
你在流血
You're bleeding.
- 什么？    - 救命！我们这里需要帮助
- What? - Help! We need help over here.
- 喔 不      - 卡梅隆
- Oh, no. - Cameron.
卡梅隆 跟我来 伙计  快
Cameron,come with me,buddy.Come on.
- 等等  卡梅隆      - 没事  你会没事的
- Wait. Cameron. - It's OK. You'll be OK.
先生 我要让你躺下
Sir,I need to lay you down.
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
躺下  躺下  你需要躺下  这不是开玩笑的
Lie down. Lie down. You need to lie down. This is serious.
不 不  挺住
No, no. Hold on.
喔 不好了！
Oh, crap!
他心跳要停了
He's gonna flatline.
这里有个人在流血
Ah, there's a man bleeding.
我在 Douglas 公园的东南区域
I'm in the south-east section of Douglas Park.
别碰我  这不是真的
Get away from me. This isn't happening.
你需要冷静  我...我不知道哪里出错了
You have to calm down. I'm... I'm not sure what's wrong.
先生 我想我找到你的问题在哪了
Sir.I think I've found your problem.
对不起 老大
I'm sorry, boss.
你的所有指数都破表了 我们必须把你拉出来
Your EKGs were off the chart, OK, so we had to pull you out.
好吧 我不会说 我已经跟你说过了
Well, I'm not gonna say I told you so.
是啊 可你刚刚说了  好吧 老大
Yeah, well, you just did. Alright, boss.
我们送你去医院检查检查 好吗？
Let's get you to the hospital, get you checked out, OK?
我没事 奥利弗
I'm fine, Oliver.
你没事？
You're fine?
那里他妈的发生了什么事？
What the hell happened in there?
只不过几分钟 奥利弗
It was only a few minutes, Oliver.
几分钟？
A couple of minutes?
老大 你的心跳停了
Boss, your heart stopped.
你要去哪？
Where are you going?
丹在失业前都和卡梅隆在公园里玩
Dan used to play in the park with Cameron,
丹在失业前都和卡梅隆 在公园里玩
before he lost his job.
- 那个灵体在玩弄 卡梅隆 的渴望      - 他的渴望？
- The entity is playing into Cameron's desire. - His desire?
他从来没对孩子说过“我爱你”
That man has never said "I love you" once to that boy.
卡梅隆 不会想跟他父亲有任何牵扯 相信我
Cameron doesn't want anything to do with his father, believe me.
对 也许你不想要那样 可是我告诉你
Well, maybe you don't want that, but I'm telling you,
丹和他在公园里玩
Dan was in the park with him.
她在提供他最想要的
She's giving him what he wants.
我们必须击溃她制造的幻觉
We need to break down her illusion.
那是救回男孩唯一的方法
It's the only way to free the boy.
他父亲在哪里？
Where's his father?
- 他可能正在醉乡呢      - 我们必须带他来这里
- He's probably getting drunk. - We need to bring him here.
我不会让那人接近我的孩子
That man is not coming anywhere near my son.
- 听好了...    - 他弄断了 卡梅隆 的手臂！
- Listen... - He broke Cameron's arm!
这个灵体非常强大
This entity is strong.
可能是我遇见过最强大的
Probably the strongest I've ever encountered.
要把你的孩子救回来 我需要所有我能获得的支援
To get your son back, I'll need all the ammunition I can get.
- 不  不可能      - 可恶 听我说！
- No. It's not gonna happen. - Damn it, listen to me!
我非常接近了
I am too close.
我走了那么远
I have come too far.
你要不与我合作 要不就失去你的儿子
So you either work with me or you lose your son.
斯帕罗太太 就告诉我们去哪能找到他吧
Mrs. Sparrow, just please tell us where to find him.
有个位于第20街和斯卡伯勒路交叉路口的酒吧
There's a bar on 20th and Scarborough.
那是他经常流连的场所
That's where he usually goes.
谢谢
Thank you.
# You know, I'm so old-fashioned
- # I'm so old-fashioned... # - Hey!
我是坐轮椅的
I'm in a wheelchair.
我看得出你不是一个善于自我保护的人
I can see you're not a fan of self-preservation.
- 没剩多少可保护的      - 我听到的是自我怜悯吗？
- Not much left to preserve. - Is that self-pity I hear?
不是  那是自由 宝贝 自由
No. That's freedom, baby. Freedom.
把注意力放到重点上吧
Focus on the important shit.
找到他了
Mmm. Found him.
斯帕罗先生
Mr Sparrow.
你儿子陷入麻烦了 我要你跟我走
Your son's in trouble. I need you to come with me.
- 你是什么人？又一个律师吗？    - 我看起来像个律师吗？
- What are you, another lawyer? - Do I look like a lawyer?
你儿子陷入麻烦中了
Your son is in trouble.
我还要喝杯啤酒 所以除非你要...
I need another beer, so unless you're buying...
你真有趣
You're so funny.
你想要我打断你的胳臂吗？
You want me to break YOUR arm, huh?
我不知道他们跟你说了什么 可我从来没碰过他
I don't know what they told you, but I never touched him.
那不关我的屁事
I don't give a shit.
我说你的儿子陷入麻烦了...是因为你
I said your son's in trouble... because of you.
恩伯 博士！
Dr Ember!
住手 恩伯！
Ember, stop!
你为什么不打电话给我？
Why didn't you call me?
- 你在这儿了 不是吗？    - 老天爷 琳赛！
- You're here, aren't you? - Jesus Christ, Lindsey!
你想瞒我这事到什么时候？
How long were you gonna keep this from me?
- 为什么我要告诉你？    - 因为他是我儿子
- Why would I tell you anything? - Because he's my son!
我们调情调够了吗？
If we're done flirting here?
- 卡梅隆 需要我们      - 丹
- Cameron needs us. - Dan.
你必须跟 恩伯 博士走 立刻
You need to go with Dr Ember now.
- 告诉我 我儿子在哪？    - 很乐意
- Show me where my son is. - With pleasure.
叫他的名字
Call him by his name.
提醒他你在房间里  告诉他你爱他
Remind him you're in the room. Tell him you love him.
跟他说只有你们俩知道的事的细节
Talk about details that only you and he would know about.
OK？他会听见你的
OK? He'll hear you.
他会醒过来
He'll wake up.
- 你确定这会有效？    - 不 我不确定
- You sure this is gonna work? - No. I'm not.
- 那我为什么要这样做？    - 如果那是我儿子 我会照做
- Then why should I do this? - I would. If it were my son.
就像我说过的 我不知道他们跟你说了什么 OK
Like I said before, I don't know what they told you, OK,
但我从来没碰他 OK 从没
but I never touched him, OK, ever.
- 我从没碰过他      - 留着说给 卡梅隆 听吧
- I never touched him. - Save it for Cameron.
好吧 如果事情出了差错 我们会支援你的
Alright, we have your back - if something goes wrong,
你有不好的感觉了 我们会把你拉出来
you get a bad feeling, we'll get you out.
譬如像什么？
Like what?
会发生什么事？绿色呕吐物吗？
What's gonna happen? Like green vomit?
你是在说头完全转到背后(都是大法师的情节)？ 拜托！
Are you talking about the whole head-turning thing? Come on!
无论是什么？别碰他
No matter what, don't touch him.
- 拜托      - 丹 我是认真的
- Come on. - Dan, I mean it.
不要有身体接触  听懂了吗？
No physical contact. Do you understand me?
好吧 我不会...
Yeah, I won't...
我不会碰他
I won't touch him.
开始吧
Let's go.
卡姆Hey, Cam.
是我  老爸
It's me. It's Dad.
有一阵子了 伙计  我没...
It's been a while, buddy. I haven't...
没见到你 就像是 永远那么久似的
Haven't seen you, like, forever.
我试着打了好几次电话 你知道吗？
You know,I tried calling a few times.
我想是我的讯息没接通
I guess my messages weren't getting through.
我还记得你不会投曲球
I remember you had that sick curve ball.
就你和我在公园里
Just me and you down at the park.
你很出色 你应该试试为球队立功
You were good, man. You should try out for the team.
卡梅隆
Cameron.
我是...我是老爸
It's... it's Dad.
慢慢来
Slow and easy.
有效了  卡梅隆 回神了
It's working. Cameron's surfacing.
- 老爸？    - 是 伙计 是我 是老爸
- Dad? - Yeah, buddy, it's me. It's Dad.
卡梅隆 我很抱歉 真的很抱歉我伤害了你
Cameron, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry I hurt you.
你一定要相信我  那是个意外
You've gotta believe me. It was an accident.
如果我能挽回发生过的事 我绝对会挽回它
If I could take it back, I'd take it back.
- 有什么资料？    - 有一大堆动静
- What do we got? - There's a lot of movement.
是啊 它在到处乱跳呢
Yeah, it's bouncing around all over the place.
你发生了什么事？怎么会发生的？
What happened to you, Cameron? How did this happen?
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
什么？我听... 我听不见 伙计
What? I can't...I can't hear you, buddy.
再...再说一次
Say it... say it again.
我原谅你了 爸
I forgive you, Dad.
真的？
You do?
是的  我想再回到从前
Yeah. I want it to be like it was.
- 还能再回去吗？    - 行的  可以...
- Can it be like before? - Yeah. It can be...
可以再像从前那样  我保证
It can be like before. Promise.
我会重新振作  OK？
I'm gonna clean up. OK?
我会为你做任何事
I'll do anything for you.
我们能再去公园吗？
Can we go to the park again?
我们可以去公园
We can go to the park.
我们可以去嘉年华会  你不是想去玩吗？
We can go to a carnival. You want to go on the rides?
- 那些我们都能去      - 真的？
- We can do all that. - Really?
真的  你病一好就去 OK？
Really. Just as soon as you're better, OK?
爸 我爱你
I love you, Dad.
卡姆
Cam...
- 天呐！    - 别 退后！别碰他！
- Oh, my God! - No, stay back! Don't touch him!
喔 上帝！
Oh, God!
上帝不在这里
God is not here.
住手！别这样做  你要的是我
Stop! Don't do this. It's me you want.
请跟着我  我们的人都在楼下
Please follow me. Our people are downstairs.
你为什么说 “你要的是我”？
Why did you say, "It's me you want"?
你有事情没告诉我
There's something you're not telling me.
你来这不是为了救 卡梅隆
You're not here to help Cameron.
你是因为别的原因来的
You're here for some other reason.
- 我为什么原因来都没关系      - 丹 死了！
- Doesn't matter why I'm here. - Dan is dead!
这到底是他妈的怎么回事？
What the hell is going on here?!
告诉我 不然就滚！
Talk to me or get the hell out!
我 26 岁的时候...
When I was 26...
...我发现我睡着后...
..I discovered that when I was asleep...
...我就能进入被附身者的意识中
..I could go into the minds of the possessed.
当我发现还有其他人 跟我有一样的能力...
When I found out there were others like me...
...而他们的生活因此被搞得天翻地覆...
..and how their lives had been turned upside-down...
...我就把我的能力隐藏起来
..I kept my abilities hidden.
我只想要一个正常的人生
I just wanted a normal life.
而我也曾经得到过
And that's what I had.
不
No.
我会折磨所有你爱的人
她被附身了？
She was possessed?
她的名字是 玛姬·格兰特
Her name was Maggie Grant.
她和 卡梅隆 都是被同一个灵体附身
She was possessed by the same entity that's in Cameron.
她察觉到我的能力
She sensed my ability.
她就杀了我妻子
She killed my wife
和我 11岁大的儿子
and my 11-year-old boy.
在那之后...
After that...
...事情就无法再回头了
..there's no turning back.
我就用我一切的能力
Since then, I've used every ability I have
试图找到她并杀掉她
to try to find her and kill her.
你来这不是为了救我儿子
You're not here to help my son.
对  我不是
No. I'm not.
这么多年来 她为什么不干脆杀了你？
In all these years, why hasn't she just killed you?
还有比死亡更可怕的情况
There are fates worse than death.
我就是怕这个情况
I was afraid of this.
她在进食！
She's feeding!
- 发生什么事？    - 玛姬 在进食
- What's happening? - Maggie's feeding.
她在耗掉 卡梅隆 的能量
She's consuming Cameron's energy.
我们要赶快了
We need to move fast.
老大！老大！
Boss! Boss!
那孩子最多只剩两小时了
The kid's got maybe two hours max.
- 该怎么做？    - 别让任何人接近他
- What's the call? - Don't let anyone near him.
尽一切力量保住他的命
Do whatever it takes to keep him alive.
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?
去拿我需要用来结束这事的能力极限
To get the edge I need to end this.
别熄火
Keep it running.
费利克斯
Felix!
Hello? Felix?
费利克斯
Felix?
费利克斯 你在吗？
Felix, you here?
费利克斯
Felix!
Felix! Felix.
我是 恩伯
It's Ember.
- 发生了什么事？    - 我正在多收集一些血
- What happened? - I was harvesting more blood.
他挣脱了束衣 弄开了门闩
He broke through the straitjacket and bolted.
- 你伤在哪里？    - 这不是我的血  我弄伤了他
- Where are you hurt? - It's not my blood. I cut him.
恩伯 我们必须离开这里  我想他还在这儿
Ember, we gotta get out of here. I think he's still here.
好 我们走
Alright. Let's move.
Whoops.
费利克斯...
Felix...
不
No.
- 退后      - 不然呢？
- Stay back. - Or what?
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
恩伯 如果你...
Ember, if only you...
费利克斯?费利克斯
Felix? Felix.
玛姬 自己要你
Maggie wants you for herself.
- 不 费利克斯      - 她将要耗尽你
- No, Felix. - She's gonna consume you.
- 费利克斯!    - 祈祷你会很容易就死了
- Felix!    - Pray you die so easily.
费利克斯！不！
Felix! No!
你去哪里了？
Where have you been?
我去拿一样东西
I had to get something.
- 他情况怎样？    - 稳定了
- How is he? - He's stable.
- 你离开后他就没动过      - 好 我们走
- He hasn't moved since you left. - Alright, let's go.
你想去哪里？
Where do you think you're going?
- 我要再回去      - 不 你不可以
- I'm going back in. - No, you're not.
我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
我不知道你去哪了
Look,I don't know where you went,
可你不能再回去  我会叫上我的人马
but you're not gonna go back in - I'm calling in my people.
如果你先前叫来的人制得了它 事情就已经结束了
If you were gonna call in your people, you'd have done it.
如果这灵体玩够了这孩子
What happens when this entity's
决定换到别人身上 怎么办？
done with the kid and decides to jump?
- 她不会      - 为什么不？
- She's not gonna jump. - Why not?
因为她要的是我  我是她的乐趣
Because it's me she wants. I'm sport to her.
所以我是你目前最好的人选
Which is why I'm your best shot right now.
我需要一样属于 卡梅隆 的物品
I need a physical item of Cameron's.
- 对他有特殊意义的东西      - 为什么？
- Something special to him. - Why?
我们需要一个她无法扭曲的真相
We need to find a truth that she can't distort,
他心中绝对不会质疑的真相
intimate truth that he won't question.
那是我们粉碎他幻觉的唯一机会
It's our only chance of shattering his illusion,
拉他出来
pulling him out.
这支戒指 你知道在哪里吗？
This ring - you know where it is?
卡梅隆 以前都把它放在床边
Cameron used to keep this by his bed.
我们离开后 我把它拿走了
And when we left, I took it away.
我尽可能地除去所有能关联到他父亲东西
I wanted as few traces of his father as possible.
我想不出有任何其他的东西...
I can't think of anything...
..卡梅隆 更珍惜...
..Cameron treasured more than this...
..蠢戒指
..stupid ring.
你随时都可以叫我闭嘴 可是...
You can tell me to shut up any time you want, but, uh...
我认为 卡梅隆 爱他的父亲 可是...
I think Cameron loves his father, but...
我的意思是 那并不表示他不爱你
I mean, that doesn't mean he doesn't love you.
我想 卡梅隆 可能不知道如何表达 可是...
I mean, Cameron might not know how to say it, but...
我是说 你是他的磐石
I mean, you're his rock.
你是他的一切
You're his entire world.
现在 他比任何时候都需要你
He needs you now more than ever.
琳赛
Lindsey...
...我需要你...
..I need you...
...坚强起来
..to be strong.
我们接近成功了  她不该杀死丹
We're getting close. She shouldn't have killed Dan.
玛姬 越来越草率了 我们要利用这点对付她
Maggie's getting sloppy and we will use that against her.
我要把你的孩子救回来
I'm gonna get your son back.
我以为你根本不关心
I thought you didn't care.
是啊 其实...
Yeah, well...
我说谎了
I lied.
拿着
Here.
你确定要这样？
You sure about this?
如果我把孩子救出来 但我仍然陷在里面
If I get the boy out and I'm still down,
你就给我注射这个
you get that into my IV.
有效的话 它能给我足够的时间
If it works, it'll buy me just enough time.
足够做什么的时间？
Enough time for what?
足够的时间把事情搞定
Enough time to get the job done.
都听你的 老大
Whatever you say, boss.
奥利弗 你带了纳洛酮吗？
Oliver, you got the Narcan?
有
Yeah.
在这儿 随时能用
Right here. Ready to go.
给我看看
Let me see it.
已经不再需要它了
Won't be needing this anymore.
我希望你都告过别了
I hope you said your goodbyes.
因为你回不来了
Because you won't be coming back.
可能吧
Maybe.
但你也是
But neither will you.
先生？先生？
Sir? Sir?
你到底要不要拿票？
Are you gonna take your ticket or not?
好 开始了
Alright. Here we go.
卡姆 看那个 看起来不错 伙计
Cam, look at that.That looks good, man.
嘿 卡梅隆  来些棉花糖如何？
Hey, Cameron. How about some cotton candy?
喔！天呐 我永远没法习惯这个
Oh! Jesus, I will never get used to that.
还用你说！
You're telling me.
卡梅隆
Cameron!
- 是公园的那个人      - 别担心
- It's the guy from the park. - No worries.
卡梅隆 我是来救你的
Cameron, I'm here to help you.
在有人受伤前 你还是滚开吧
Why don't you back off before someone gets hurt?
这不是你父亲 卡梅隆  这都不是真的
This is not your father, Cameron. This is not real.
- 我不懂你在说什么？    - 我知道这很困惑
- What are you talking about? - I know it's confusing.
你必须相信我
You're just gonna have to trust me.
- 爸！    - 离我儿子远点
- Dad!    - Get away from my son.
知道吗 你的下场会很糟 伙计
You know what, this is gonna end badly for you, man.
卡梅隆 别害怕  你还记得这戒指吗？
Cameron, don't be afraid. Do you remember this ring?
你以前都戴着它睡觉 记得吗？
You used to sleep with it, remember?
- 爸？    - 那不是你爸 卡梅隆
- Dad?    - It's not your dad, Cameron.
它看起来像你爸 对你说所有你爱听的话
It looks like your dad, saying everything you want to hear.
- 可是它不是你爸      - 把戒指给我 卡梅隆
- But it's not your father. - Give me the ring, Cameron.
你知不知道 你是个讨厌的疯子
You know what, you're a frickin' psycho.
你离我儿子远点
You stay away from my son.
孩子 你知道我永远不会伤害你的 是吗？
You know I'd never hurt you, son. OK?
我爱你 卡梅隆
I love you, Cameron.
卡梅隆
Cameron?
你父亲从来没说过他爱你
Your father could never say he loved you.
你听他说过这话吗？
You ever heard him say those words?
别听他的卡姆  OK？
Don't listen to him, Cam. OK?
嘿 我叫你滚开
Hey. I said get out of here.
你比谁都了解你父亲
You know your dad better than anyone.
这不是你爸
This is not your dad.
别听他的 卡梅隆
Don't listen to him, Cameron.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. Sorry.
怎么了,卡姆？
What's wrong, Cam?
爸？
Dad?
怎么了 伙计？你为什么那样看我？
What's wrong, buddy? Why you looking at me like that?
它不是你爸 卡梅隆
It's not your dad, Cameron.
这家伙在唬弄你 卡姆
This guy's done something to you, Cam.
- 别靠近我      - 我永远不会伤害你的
- Stay away from me. - I would never hurt you.
永远
Ever.
你不是我爸
You're not my dad.
卡梅隆 别跑！
Cameron, stop!
他还有四分钟
He's coming up on four minutes.
卡梅隆
Cameron!
- 别靠近我！    - 卡梅隆! 卡梅隆 信任我
- Stay away from me! - Cameron! Cameron, trust me.
- 我不会伤害你 OK？    - 这是怎么回事？
- I'm not gonna hurt you, OK? - What's happening?
卡梅隆
Cameron!
来！
Come on!
卡梅隆
Cameron!
回来 卡梅隆!
Come back, Cameron!
- 回来！    - 快  我们要继续跑
- Come back! - Come on. We gotta keep moving.
别相信他！他是坏人
Don't trust him! He's a bad man!
他要伤害你
He wants to hurt you.
- 卡梅隆！    - 嘘！没事的
- Cameron!    - Shh! It's OK.
- 我是怎么了？    - 你没有问题
- What's wrong with me? - There's nothing wrong with you.
- 这不是真的      - 感觉很真实啊
- This isn't real. - It feels real.
那是因为你相信它
That's because you believe it.
别再相信
Stop believing it
我向你保证 它就会消失了
and I promise you it'll go away.
你可以让这一切都消失
You can make all of this disappear.
只要你听我的  你做得到吗？
I just need you to listen to me. Can you do that?
好...好吧
O...OK.
好  你有最喜欢的颜色吗？
OK. Do you have a favourite colour?
- 蓝色      - 真好 我也是
- Blue. - Oh, that's good. Mine too.
你看到那个蓝色的门吗？
You see that blue door?
那是你的世界 卡梅隆
It's your world, Cameron.
你可以控制那里面的一切
You can control everything in it.
那是让你出去的路
It's your way out.
快  你妈在等你
Hurry.Your mom's waiting for you.
去吧 没事的
Go ahead. It's gonna be OK.
现在你麻烦了 卡梅隆
Now you're in trouble, Cameron.
进那门去 卡梅隆 马上！
Go through the door, Cameron, now!
你不会有第二次机会了
You won't get another chance.
- 他剩不到一分钟了      - 他弄得太紧急了
- He's got less than a minute. - He's cutting it too close.
喔 加油 老大
Oh, come on, boss.
进那门去！进那门去！
Go through the door! Go through the door!
我玩够那小鬼了
I'm done with the boy.
现在我要玩孵出他的那婊子
I'm going after the bitch that spawned him.
你只能去一个地方
There's only one place you're going.
而我要把你一起拖去
Yeah. And I'm taking you with me.
记得这个吗？
You remember this?
记得吗？
Remember?
你害死她的那个晚上 我妻子就戴着它
My wife was wearing this the night you killed her.
现在我要你戴
I want you to wear it now.
10秒
10 seconds.
卡梅隆
Cameron!
不！
No!
卡梅隆！你做到了！
Cameron! You did it!
卡梅隆
Cameron?
妈！
Mom!
喔...谢谢你
Oh... Thank you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿 老大
Hey, boss.
我竖了几只手指？
How many fingers am I holding up?
把你的拇指从我脸前拿开
Get your thumb out of my face.
你没事了 老大
You're gonna be just fine, boss.
现在我们可以休个假了吗？
Can we take a vacation now?
爸？你听得见我吗？
Dad? Can you hear me?
是你吗 爸？
Is it you, Dad?
爸？
Dad?
爸？爸！
Dad? Dad!
爸？爸？
Dad? Dad?
妈！爸醒了
Mom! Dad's awake.
- 嘿      - 我在哪？安娜
- Hey.    - Where am I? Anna?
你听得见我们？
Can you hear us?
- 发生什么事了？    - 我们出了一场车祸
- What happened? - We were in a car accident.
- 车开出了马路      - 一个女人撞了我们
- The car went off the road. - A woman hit us.
不 不 亲爱的  你闪避一个在慢跑的人
No, no, honey. You swerved around a jogger.
你不记得了
You don't remember.
你有脑震荡
You had a concussion.
医生说你可能会有些迷惘
The doctor said that you might be disoriented.
你昏迷了三天
You were in a coma for three days.
- 你怎么样？伙计      - 很好
- How you doing, buddy?    - Good.
是吗？
Yeah?
感觉好真实
Felt so real.
一切都会好的
Everything's gonna be OK.
- 亲爱的 走这里      - 嘿 爸
- Honey, this way.    - Hey, Dad.
回家以后我们玩一对一？
So you up for some one-on-one when we get home?
他不能打篮球 亲爱的  他需要休息
No basketball for him, honey. He needs to rest.
那我们可以在 Wii上玩吗？
Then can we play on the Wii?
我喜欢 杰克
I'd like that, Jake.
我爱你
I love you.
亲爱的 怎么了？
Honey, what's wrong?
爸 什么事？
Dad, what is it?
怎么了？
What's wrong?
不
No.
你们不是真的
You're not real.
塞斯 塞斯 别这么说
Seth. Seth, don't say that.
我爱你们
I love you both.
- 你们不是真的      - 爸！
- You're not real.    - Dad!
- 塞斯 回来！    - 爸！
- Seth, come back!    - Dad!
要去哪吗？
Going somewhere?
玛姬
Maggie.
喔 糟了！
Oh, shit!
- 不！    - 玛姬！
- No!    - Maggie!
你为什么不干脆杀了我？
Why don't you just kill me?
因为我要你受伤害 塞斯
Because I want you to hurt, Seth.
我要你感到痛苦
I want you to know pain.
你将要焚身了 塞斯
You're gonna burn, Seth.
思考！思考！思考！
Think! Think! Think!
喔 上帝！
Oh, my God!
放他走
Let him go.
我就不再抵抗
I'll stop fighting.
我就是你的
You can have me.
放掉他 否则我就跳下去
Release him or I'll jump.
开门！
Open the door!
- 开门 卡梅隆！    - 卡梅隆！
- Open the door, Cameron!    - Cameron!
卡梅隆 伙计 我们需要你把门打开
Cameron, buddy, we need you to open the door.
卡梅隆 我们需要你把门打开
Cameron, we need you to open this door.
- 卡梅隆！    - 你听得见我吗？伙计
- Cameron!    - Can you hear me, buddy?
你听得见我吗？快来把门打开
Can you hear me? Just come open the door.
你不是叫我示弱吧？是吗 奥利弗？
You're not going soft on me, are you, Oliver?
老大？
Boss?
注射进去了！
It's injected!
老大...
Boss...
老大？
Boss?
不！
No!
你完了 臭婊子！
You end now, bitch!
不！
No!
不！不！别碰他！别碰他！
No! No! Don't touch him! Don't touch him!
我们走！
Let's move!
要来了  他休克了  清场！
Here we go. The guy's in shock. Clear!
要来了  清场！
Here we go. Clear!
加油 恩伯 奋斗
Come on, Ember, fight.
要再来一次  清场
Here we go again. Clear.
- 我很抱歉      - 不 不 就...
- I'm sorry.    - No, no, just...
- 就再来一次      - 女士
- Just one more time.    - Ma'am.
现在！
Now!
好 清场
There, all clear.
清场！
Clear!
老天 有脉搏了
Oh, my God. We've got a pulse.
有节奏了！
We've got a rhythm!
好  再拿另一袋来
Alright. Let's get another bag here.
预计多久到达？
What's our ETA?
我们要失去他了！
We're losing him!
他又休克了  清场！
Guy's in shock. Clear!
# Sail!
# This is how I show my love
# I made it in my mind because
# Blame it on my ADD, baby
# This is how an angel dies
# Blame it on my own sick pride
# Blame it on my ADD, baby
# Sail
# Maybe I should cry for help
# Maybe I should kill myself
# Myself
# Blame it on my ADD, baby
# Sail! #